We are joined by our headliner of the week, Vic Jagger.
Yes, our new DC affiliate, Magic1023927.
Vic is a veteran on their airwaves.
And we are in the midst of the hot topic of the hour,
which is Sean Puffy Combs.
Vic, why do you think people are so kind of quick to jump on this
in your knowledge of the history of Puff within the industry?
I think that these are things that people always wanted to say.
And they were just scared.
If you think back to people saying anything about Puff or anybody powerful.
Russell Simmons.
Right.
In the industry, their jobs were at risk.
And I think now it's just kind of accepted that people can just say,
oh, this happened to me too.
Well, I guess me too movement.
Maybe that's what it is.
Honestly, when it hit Hollywood and I was like, uh-oh.
If it turns over here to the music industry,
it's going to be a lot of people that are worried.
And there are still a lot of hip-hop artists that are worried because that was the culture.
A lot of women, a lot of drugs, a lot of partying, and just a lot of recklessness.
Why do you think people were sweating about Freakness?
They were scared that they were going to be on there.
These are fathers and mothers and pastors now.
And so I think that people are just now feeling more open enough to put people out there.
We are.